[{"answer": "Well, I think it's a shame.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 3, "question": "What do you think of Donald Trump banging on about this every day at the moment?", "qSentId": 2}, {"answer": "Yes, he is.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "He is, isn't he?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "I can.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "Can you still do that?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "Yes, well, he's made it so family is very important to him and to Michelle and --", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "The one that no one's allowed to touch?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "Yes, I think --", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "Is that what you can't do anymore?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "I think it's unfortunate.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "What do you think of that?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's a shame.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 79, "question": "What do you think of Donald Trump banging on about this every day at the moment?", "qSentId": 78}, {"answer": "Very big brotherly.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "What's he always been like to you as a brother?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "Did he?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "You know, I did, eventually.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "Did you listen to him or not?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "Well, I would say that he needs to be more cheerful when he loses to me in Scrabble.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "Go on, you could do better here?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "Well, I wept profusely as you might imagine, but I also -- our grandmother had just passed away.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "What was it like when he actually got in?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "Both of our, you know, our motherly elders, both our mom and our grandma would have been tremendously proud.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "What would she have made, do you think, of him as president?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "I don't think anybody can be fully prepared.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "Is anybody prepared?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "OETORO-NG: That's -- you know, that's an interesting question.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "Would you be happy as a sister to see him run again?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "He knew that there would be things that might upset me and he reminded me before he elected to run for president not to get too riled up and not to take it too personally.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "But when it gets very personal, do you feel that anger boiling up as his sister?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "You know --", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "When you get together for Christmas, I mean who does the cooking and stuff?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "It's not a bad excuse.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "It's not a bad excuse, is it?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "There are sort of three messages.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "What is the message you'd like your daughters to take from this book, do you think?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "I can't possibly.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "Are you hoping to outdo him with this one?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "I hope -- you know, I hope so.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 257, "question": "Fighting the good fight?", "qSentId": 256}, {"answer": "But I'm ready to go.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "You're ready to go?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "Is he going to win?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "I -- he needs to win.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "You like to win, don't you?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "I think he -- I think he really does enjoy seeing a problem and being able to fix it.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "Or is it just a relentless challenge?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "Well, yes.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "This would seem to suggest that the economy, which was the central plank of that argument, is in a right old mess, isn't it?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "Well, last year, Piers, they took in at the federal government level a little over $2 trillion in revenue and they spent $3.7 trillion.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "What percentage of the problem that America now finds itself in economically is down to the Republican administration of the previous eight years, would you say?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, when he was a United States senator and he faced this issue as a sitting senator, he said that raising the debt ceiling was a sign of flawed leadership.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "Well, I think there's -- and that sentiment, of course, is very raw and it's very real as I travel across the country.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "What's your view of that?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think it's government's job to micromanage salaries in the private sector nor do I support tax increases, and my record is pretty clear on that.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "Would you like to see an element of those bonuses being plowed back into the general economy?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "No, I didn't.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "I mean, did you not feel slightly unsavory when that was done?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "Well, I'm just -- for me just getting known, Piers.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "Did you ever imagine in your wildest nightmares that you'd see a poll of potential Republican candidates which had you at two percent and Donald Trump at 19 percent?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "Yeah, I could have the big flop or the mullet.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "Do you think it may come down to the hair, do you, governor?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "You're talking to somebody who is the governor of the state that elected Jesse Ventura as governor and Al Franken as senator.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "Do you sense that happening, that there is this vacuum?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "I do, Piers.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "Do you believe that President Obama was born in Hawaii?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "I'm running for president.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "In a hypothetical scenario, governor, if someone like Donald Trump was to emerge as the Republican nominee, and asked you to be vice president, would you accept that honor?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "Well, I have an exploratory committee up and running.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "Can we take that as an official announcement?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "Well, I think, Piers, they've been working hard to deal with a very difficult situation.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "Is that fair?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "Well, I want to be clear, Piers.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "Not just in Japan, but perhaps to America and to the wider world?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "Well, we have really a two-pronged approach that we're going to use to take a look at that very question.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "Do you see fundamental changes as a result of what we've seen in Japan?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, we have a team of experts that is in Tokyo, that is interfacing very closely with experts from the Japanese government and experts from the industry and utility in Japan.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "But should we be getting quite critical now of the level of information coming out of the Japanese authorities?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "Yeah, we have strong confidence that there really is no likelihood of any kind of significant impact to the United States or any Hawaii or Alaska or any of the territories of the United States.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "Is it 100 percent certain that there is going to be no risk here to Americans, for example, on the coastline here?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "Well, right now, the focus is on making sure that the reactors stay cool and that the spent fuel pools can be put in a safe, stable configuration.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "How do you deal with this kind of leak?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "We think the plants in this country are safe and they continue to operate safely.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "Are you 100 percent satisfied that America is prepared for that kind of eventuality, or even a bigger earthquake and tsunami?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "Almost.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "Good morning, Katie, I think it is for you, isn't it?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Well, the name on everyone's list is still Sara Boson (ph) from the queen.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "Do we have any indication of who's made the wedding dress yet?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "The guest list is fascinating.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "What about the guest list for what the going to be the wedding of the millennium?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "I think it's going to be fantastic.", "docId": "110412pmt", "aSentId": 594, "question": "And the world media and the world itself will be watching what I think is going to be a quite extraordinary and hopefully uplifting event, isn't it?", "qSentId": 593}]